Guide to the UH Business Manager (McElhinney) Records
University of Houston Libraries
UH Business Manager (McElhinney) Records
1945-1973
1985-001
McElhinney, Charles Flemming; University of Houston. Business Manager
18.00 Linear Feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
The Business Manager Records of C. F. McElhinney are the records McElhinney generated during his tenure at the University of Houston (1945-1973).
Biographical Information:
Charles Flemming McElhinney (commonly known as C. F. McElhinney or “Mr. Mac”) was born on Sept. 19, 1907 in Truro, Nova Scotia. He received a bachelor’s degree from Acadia University in 1926 at the age of eighteen and taught in public schools in Canada before continuing his graduate studies. He received a master of arts degree from Columbia University in 1928.
Mr. McElhinney taught in the public school systems in Chester Basin and Halifax, Nova Scotia before moving to the United States. He was an assistant professor at the State Teachers College in Troy, Alabama from 1930-1931 and at the Mississippi State College for Women from 1931-1934. He moved to Houston in 1934, taking the position of assistant director of curriculum and research for the Houston Independent Schools District from 1934-1939. Mr. McElhinney then became the director of research from 1939-1945, when he became the business manager for the University of Houston, which until 1945 had been operated by the Houston Independent School District. During this time he also served as a staff assistant to Mr. E. E. Oberholtzer, the president of the University.
From 1945 until his retirement in 1973, Mr. McElhinney served as the business manager of the University. During this time, he was given the position of vice-president and business manager from 1950-1962, and was senior vice president for finance and treasurer from 1962-1973. He also served as interim president of the University from 1953-1954.
During Mr. McElhinney’s years at the University, he also served as a faculty member in the department of education, and as a sponsor of several student activities and programs. Additionally he was the coach of the first athletic team fielded by the University (ice hockey) in 1934 while the University was still known as the Houston Junior College.
When Mr. McElhinney retired in 1973 (at the end of the fiscal year), the Board of Regents renamed the Graduate Studies building in honor of McElhinney’s decades of service to the University.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
University of Houston; University of Houston -- Administration
Genre/Form of Material:
Administrative records; Business records
Acquisition Information:
Transfer
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research.
Scope and Contents
The Business Manager Records of C. F. McElhinney are the records McElhinney generated during his tenure at the University of Houston (1945-1973). The collection has been arranged into six series: Board of Regents, Staff Conference Meetings, Legislative Activities, Building Files, President’s Office, and the Houston College for Negroes. The materials in the collection date from 1945-1974, with the bulk of the materials dating from the 1960s and 1970s. Included in the collection are university-related correspondence, minutes, agendas, reports, financial reports, bids, and contracts. There are no photographs or personal papers in the collection.
Key correspondents in the collection include C. F. McElhinney, Philip Hoffman, Patrick J. Nicholson, E. E. Oberholtzer, W. W. Kemmerer, and Clanton W. Williams.
The materials follow the organization in which McElhinney left them, with some minor rearrangement within folders to follow chronological order. All folder titles use the headings provided by McElhinney.
Materials in the collection document the administrative activities of the University, including Camp Wheeler, construction on the Houston College for Negroes campus (now Texas Southern University), the legislative activities of the University during its campaign for state support in the 1960s, the development of KUHT Channel 8 and KUHF, the campus radio station.
Oversized materials, including maps of campus from the 1960s, blueprints and related architectural materials on the UH Central Power Plant, and a campus map of the utility distribution system have been removed from the collection for preservation purposes. Please ask an Archives staff member for assistance regarding oversize materials.
Detailed List of Contents
- Board of Regents, 1945-1973
  Scope and Contents
  This is the largest series, 10.5 boxes or 488 folders, with the bulk of the records dating from the 1950s through 1973. The materials are arranged in chronological order with some exceptions and include agendas, minutes, memoranda, reports, budgets and financial reports. Also included in this series are the records of several sub-committees of the Board of Regents/Board of Governors. These include the committees on which McElhinney served: the Finance Committee, the Executive Committee, the Building Committee, the Planning Committee, and the Investment Committee. During 1957 some re-organization was undertaken, which created a Board of Governors to serve in an advisory capacity to the Board of Regents. This changed again in 1963, when the University of Houston gained state funding and the Board of Governors was eliminated. Generally the files are organized by month, with agendas and any attached materials followed by the minutes for that meeting. Of particular interest are materials attached to the minutes and agendas, which include reports or memos from many of the faculty and administrators on campus. These reports address the initiation of new programs on campus as well as several major issues: construction on campus, desegregation, the campaign for state support in the early 1960s, Camp Wheeler, KUHT, and KUHF. These materials have been left with the agendas with which they were attached and therefore are found throughout the series. Materials on KUHT and KUHF, in particular, are scattered throughout this series, although there is a folder from the Ad-Hoc Television Committee in 1959 and a folder specifically on KUHT from 1966.
  - Act Creating Board of Regents, 1945-1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Regents, March-May 1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Regents, June-December 1945 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Regents, January-June 1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Regents, July-December 1946 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Regents, January-February 1947 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Regents, March 19, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Regents, April-May 1947 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Regents, June 18, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Regents, September 17, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Regents, October-December 1947 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Regents, January-April 1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Regents, May 19, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Regents, June 16, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Regents, September 15, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Regents, October 20, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Regents, November-December 1948 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Regents, January-May 1949 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Regents, August 23, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Regents, September 27, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Regents, November 22, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Regents, January 24, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Regents, February 21, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Regents, March 21, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Regents, April 18, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Regents, May 16, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Executive Conference Agenda, June 15, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Executive Conference Minutes, June 15, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Regents, July 18, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Regents, August 15, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Regents, September 19, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Regents, October 17, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Regents, November 21, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Regents, December 19, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Regents, January 16, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Regents, February 20, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Regents, March 20, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Regents, April 17, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Regents, May 22, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Regents, June 19, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Legislative Acts – Creating Board of Regents, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Rules and Regulations – UH, [1951?] (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Regents, July 17, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Regents, September 18, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Regents, October 23, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Regents, December 18, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Regents, January 22, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Regents, February 19, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Regents, March 18, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Regents, April 15, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Regents, May 20, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Regents, June 16, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Regents, September 16, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Regents, October 21, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Regents, November 21, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Regents, December 16, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Regents, January 27, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Regents, February 17, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Regents, February 23, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Regents, March 17, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Regents, April 28, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Regents, May 19, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Regents, June 23, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Regents, July 22, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Regents, September 2, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Regents, October 20, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Regents, November 17, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Regents, December 15, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Regents, January 27, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Regents, February 16, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Regents, March 11, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Regents, April 20, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Regents, May 18, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Regents, June 15, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Regents, September 21, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Regents, October 19, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Regents, November 16, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Regents, December 6, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Regents, January 17, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Regents, February 15, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Regents, March 15, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Regents, April 28, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Regents, May 26, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Regents, June 20, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Regents, September 19, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Regents, October 17, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Regents, December 5, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Regents, January 16, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Regents, February 27, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Regents, March 19, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Regents, April 16, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Regents, May 21, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Regents, June 12, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Regents, September 17, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Regents, October 15, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Regents, December 10, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Governors Organizational Meeting, January 21, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee, January 21, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee, February 11, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee, March 11, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee, April 8, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Governors, April 15, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Governors, April 15, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Executive Committee, May 13, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Executive Committee, June 10, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Governors, June 17, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Finance Committee, July 17, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Executive Committee, July 29, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Finance Committee, September 24, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Finance Committee, October 7, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Executive Committee, October 14, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Planning Committee, October 16, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Governors, October 21, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Planning Committee, October 30, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Executive Committee, December 9, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Executive Committee, January 13, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Governors, January 20, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Ad Hoc Status of Departments Committee, February 3 and March 24, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Executive Committee, March 10, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Executive Committee, April 15, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Governors, April 22, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee, May 12, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Governors, June 16, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee, September 8, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Finance Committee, October 6 and 9, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Governors, October 20, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, November 10, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Comparison of Non-instructional Salaries with Houston Area Business, December 8, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Special Meeting, December 9, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee, January 12, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee, February 9, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Ad Hoc Television Committee, March 5, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Combined, April 20, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee, May 11, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Governors, June 15, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee, September 28, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Financial Statements (special meeting and follow-up correspondence), October 14, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee, October 26, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Governors, November 20, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Executive Committee, December 28, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Executive Committee, January 20, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, February 10, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Executive Committee, February 22, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Governors, April 25, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee, May 23, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Combined, June 27, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Coordinating Committee, September 7, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Executive Committee, September 27, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Executive Committee, October 24, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Combined, November 28, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Executive Committee, January 18, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Special Combined, January 23, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Building and Grounds Committee, March 23, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Executive Committee, March 28, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Executive Committee, April 19, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Governors, April 24, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Executive Committee, May 22, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Special Meeting, May 30, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Special Combined, July 25, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Executive Committee, September 26, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Executive Committee, October 23, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Governors, November 27, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Ad Hoc Budget Committee, January 19, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Executive Committee, January 22, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Executive Committee, March 27, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Combined, April 30, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Executive Committee, May 28, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Ad Hoc Research Committee, July 25, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Special Executive Committee, July 30, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Special Executive Committee, September 7, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Special Meeting on Emergency Building Needs, September 21, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Combined, September 25, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Research and Development Committee, October 25, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, October 29, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, December 10, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Research and Development Committee, December 10, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, January 28, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee, February 28, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee, March 26, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - House Bill No. 291, March 27, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Combined, April 23, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Senate Bill No. 2 (September 1, 1963), May 23, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, May 27, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, July 1, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Special Executive and Regents (state support), August 14, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Act creating the University of Houston as a State-Supported Institution, September 1, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Biennial Report of the President, 1961-1962, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Board of Regents Meeting Schedule, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Worksheets – Resolutions, etc., September 1, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Regents Organizational Meeting, September 11, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Resolution Approval and Payment of All Accounts, Signed, September 11, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Resolution Approval and Payment of All Accounts, Blank, September 11, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Authorizing Preparation and Signature on Documents Covering the Procurement and Use of Tax-free Alcohol, September 11, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Authorizing Temporary Investments of Free Cash Balances, September 11, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Authority to Approve Travel Signed Copies, September 11, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Concerning Sale and Endorsement of Securities, Signed Copies, September 11, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Concerning Sale and Endorsement of Securities, Blank, September 11, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Ratifying and Confirming Obligations, Acts, and Personnel Policies of Previous Board of Regents (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Act Creating the University as a State-supported Institution and By-laws of the Board of Regents, September 1963 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Building Committee, October 10, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Regents, October 21, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Building Committee, October 21, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Regents Terms of Office, October 24, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Regents, November 18, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Executive Committee, December 9, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Regents, December 16, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Resolution Concerning sale and Endorsement of securities, Signed, December 16, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Building Committee, December 16, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Resolution University of Houston Construction Account, December 16, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Non-instructional Personnel List, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Regents, January 20, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Resolution Approval and Payment of All Accounts, Signed Copies, January 20, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Resolution Approval and Payment of All Accounts, Blank, January 20, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Resolution Concerning Sale and Endorsement of Securities, Signed, January 20, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - U.S. Naval Reserve Training Center re: Acquisition of Property, January 20, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Building Committee, January 20, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - J.G. Twiney cancelled contract, January 10, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Regents, February 17, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Building Committee, February 17, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Regents, March 16, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Resolution Approval and Payments of All Accounts – Signed, March 16, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Resolution Concerning the Sale and Endorsement of Securities, Signed, March 16, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Building Committee, March 16, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Special Regents, April 7, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Special Building Committee Meeting, April 7, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Regents, April 20, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Resolution Concerning the Sale and Endorsement of Securities, Signed, April 20, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - University of Houston Educational and General Budget 1964-1965, April 20, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Regents Terms of Office, May 18, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Building Committee, May 18, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Building Committee, June 15, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Regents, June 30, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Regents, December 14, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Regents, September 21, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Building Committee, September 21, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Regents, October 19, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Building Committee, October 19, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Finance Committee, November 16, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Regents, November 18, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Building Committee, November 18, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Building Committee, December 14, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Regents, January 18, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Building Committee, January 18, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Regents, February 15, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Regents, March 15, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Building Committee, March 15, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Regents, April 19, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Building Committee, April 19, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Regents, May 24, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1965-1966 Faculty Salary List, Board List, May 24, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Building Committee, May 24, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Personnel Recommendations, May 1965 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Finance Committee, June 21, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Regents, July 26, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Building Committee, July 26, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Special Regents, August 11, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Personnel List, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Statement-Current Salaries-Administrators, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Meeting Schedule, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Regents, September 28, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Building Committee, September 28, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Regents, November 2, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Building Committee, November 2, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Regents, December 7, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Building Committee, December 7, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Regents, January 4, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Building Committee, January 4, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Regents, February 1, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Building Committee, February 1, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Regents, March 1, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Building Committee, March 1, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - University Oaks–Letter re: Encroachment on University property, March 27, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Regents, April 5, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Building Committee, April 5, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Regents, May 3, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Building Committee, May 3, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Personnel Recommendations 1966-1967, May 1966 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Executive Committee, June 7, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Building Committee, July 13, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Special Meeting, July 13, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Notice of Special Meeting of Austin, Texas, Unsigned, July 26, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Notice of Special Meeting of Austin, Texas, Signed, July 26, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Special Meeting, Austin, Texas, July 26, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Building Committee, Austin, Texas, July 26, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Resolution-UH Science-Research Building, July 26, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Resolution-UH-Constitutional Building Fund, July 26, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Building Committee-Wood and Tower Proposals, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Regents, September 6, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Building Committee, September 6, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Finance Committee, September 14, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Regents, October 4, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Building Committee, October 4, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - KUHT, December 6, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Regents, December 6, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Building Committee, December 6, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Regents, January 3, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Building Committee, January 3, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)